<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Mosaddeq on Alireza Yoonesi</title>
    <link>https://en.AYoonesi.ir/tags/mosaddeq/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Mosaddeq on Alireza Yoonesi</description>
    <image>
      <title>Alireza Yoonesi</title>
      <url>https://en.AYoonesi.ir/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://en.AYoonesi.ir/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2023 19:30:01 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://en.AYoonesi.ir/tags/mosaddeq/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Coup Chronicles: Unpacking the 1953 US Iranian Drama Through Abrahamian&#39;s Critical Lens</title>
      <link>https://en.AYoonesi.ir/posts/coup-chronicles-unpacking-the-1953-us-iranian-drama-through-abrahamians-critical-lens/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2023 19:30:01 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://en.AYoonesi.ir/posts/coup-chronicles-unpacking-the-1953-us-iranian-drama-through-abrahamians-critical-lens/</guid>
      <description>In his seminal work The Coup: 1953, the CIA, and the Roots of Modern U.S.-Iranian Relations, Professor Ervand Abrahamian offers a penetrating examination of the 1953 coup in Iran that stands in stark contrast to established historical narratives like Mark J. Gasiorowski&amp;#39;s. Delving deeper into pre-coup events and British involvement, Abrahamian provides invaluable context and global perspective to understand the intricate political and economic forces at play. Though not without limitations in his sympathies toward Mossadegh and the Tudeh party, Abrahamian&amp;#39;s critical lens compels readers to reconsider prevailing interpretations and deepen their comprehension of this watershed moment&amp;#39;s complexities and far-reaching implications for U.S.-Iran relations. His accessible narrative makes the book intriguing for lay and academic audiences alike.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unveiling the Shadows of Power: Mohammad Mosaddeq and the 1953 Coup in Iran</title>
      <link>https://en.AYoonesi.ir/posts/unveiling-the-shadows-of-power-mohammad-mosaddeq-and-the-1953-coup-in-iran/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 18:50:48 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://en.AYoonesi.ir/posts/unveiling-the-shadows-of-power-mohammad-mosaddeq-and-the-1953-coup-in-iran/</guid>
      <description>Mark J. Gasiorowski&amp;#39;s magnum opus, Mohammad Mosaddeq and the 1953 Coup in Iran, is a monumental work of historical scholarship that delves into the intricacies of one of the most pivotal moments in the 20th century—a moment that shaped the course of Iranian history and had far-reaching implications for global politics. Gasiorowski&amp;#39;s book is a tour de force of meticulous research, analytical precision, and narrative sophistication. It takes the reader on a journey through the tumultuous landscape of post-World War II Iran, where the convergence of domestic politics, Cold War dynamics, and oil diplomacy set the stage for a seismic shift in power.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
