<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Alireza Yoonesi</title>
    <link>https://en.AYoonesi.ir/tags/alireza-yoonesi/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Alireza Yoonesi</description>
    <image>
      <title>Alireza Yoonesi</title>
      <url>https://en.AYoonesi.ir/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://en.AYoonesi.ir/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2023 15:05:49 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://en.AYoonesi.ir/tags/alireza-yoonesi/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>A Pragmatic Approach to Anonymity in Recent UK Supreme Court Rulings</title>
      <link>https://en.AYoonesi.ir/posts/a-pragmatic-approach-to-anonymity-in-recent-uk-supreme-court-rulings/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2023 15:05:49 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://en.AYoonesi.ir/posts/a-pragmatic-approach-to-anonymity-in-recent-uk-supreme-court-rulings/</guid>
      <description>Explore a pragmatic analysis of the recent UK Supreme Court ruling ([2023] UKSC 42) on asylum seekers and the offshore processing policy. Delve into the legal principles, ethical implications, and the court&amp;#39;s consideration of the Rwandan asylum system. Discover the nuanced perspective on the law&amp;#39;s application, procedural flaws, and the potential challenges of extra-territorial asylum policies. Join the discussion on the delicate balance between legality and ethics in the context of refugee rights and the evolving landscape of asylum law.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Revisiting the Sociopolitical Thought of Muhammad Ali Foroughi: Lessons for Today&#39;s Patriotic Intellectuals</title>
      <link>https://en.AYoonesi.ir/posts/revisiting-the-sociopolitical-thought-of-muhammad-ali-foroughi-lessons-for-todays-patriotic-intellectuals/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Nov 2023 15:50:07 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://en.AYoonesi.ir/posts/revisiting-the-sociopolitical-thought-of-muhammad-ali-foroughi-lessons-for-todays-patriotic-intellectuals/</guid>
      <description>The multifaceted life of Muhammad Ali Foroughi, one of the most influential statesmen and #intellectuals in #Iran&amp;#39;s contemporary #history, provides valuable insights that remain strikingly relevant today. While a comprehensive examination of this complex figure is beyond the scope of this essay, a reflective analysis reveals important lessons for responding rationally in periods of turmoil. The original Persian essay provides invaluable perspectives for assessing this statesman whose sophisticated mind embraced both Eastern wisdom and Western learning. By transcending parochial biases and reflecting deeply on the past, we gain vision to navigate the uncertainties of the present. The tortuous course of history ultimately exposes shortcomings in even the noblest human judgments. But #integrity and #reason remain our best guides through the shadows and into the light.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://en.AYoonesi.ir/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 03:08:28 +0330</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://en.AYoonesi.ir/contact/</guid>
      <description>Have a question, suggestion, or just want to chat about law, code, or anything in between? I&amp;#39;d love to hear from you! Feel free to drop me a message using the form below, and I&amp;#39;ll get back to you as soon as possible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://en.AYoonesi.ir/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 02:34:17 +0330</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://en.AYoonesi.ir/about/</guid>
      <description>Exploring the Nexus of Law and Code: Join me in unraveling the intricacies of Private Law and the boundless possibilities of technology at the intersection of jurisprudence and innovation.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
