<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Politics on Alireza Yoonesi</title>
    <link>https://en.AYoonesi.ir/tags/politics/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Politics on Alireza Yoonesi</description>
    <image>
      <title>Alireza Yoonesi</title>
      <url>https://en.AYoonesi.ir/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://en.AYoonesi.ir/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 15:30:03 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://en.AYoonesi.ir/tags/politics/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Thomas Hobbes and Political Obedience: Insights from the English Civil War</title>
      <link>https://en.AYoonesi.ir/posts/thomas-hobbes-and-political-obedience-insights-from-the-english-civil-war/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 15:30:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://en.AYoonesi.ir/posts/thomas-hobbes-and-political-obedience-insights-from-the-english-civil-war/</guid>
      <description>Dive into the philosophical insights of Thomas Hobbes, a prominent 17th-century English philosopher, as he explores the complexities of political obedience. Influenced by his experiences during the brutal English civil war, Hobbes emphasizes the importance of submitting to imperfect rulers to prevent chaos and violence. In his renowned work Leviathan, Hobbes merges the social contract theory with a defense of unwavering obedience, while also cautioning against the dangers of frequent revolutions. Discover how Hobbes&amp;#39;s perspectives continue to shape our understanding of governmental authority today</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Michael Munger on Constitutions</title>
      <link>https://en.AYoonesi.ir/posts/michael-munger-on-constitutions/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2023 11:30:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://en.AYoonesi.ir/posts/michael-munger-on-constitutions/</guid>
      <description>Michael Munger contends that we need rules about the rules more than we need actual rules. So, is a new Constitution required for the United States? Listen as the economist and political scientist from Duke University discusses public choice, approving of coercion, and whether or not constitutions matter with host Russ Roberts</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Iranian Kamikaze Drone — Shahed 136</title>
      <link>https://en.AYoonesi.ir/posts/iranian-kamikaze-drone-shahed-136/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 11:30:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://en.AYoonesi.ir/posts/iranian-kamikaze-drone-shahed-136/</guid>
      <description>Iranian Kamikaze drone has a price tag of fewer than twenty-five thousand dollars, which is half the average price of a car in the US and roughly one percent of the Tomahawk price tag. It appears to be a low-cost cruise missile that can be effective when fired in groups. How does it work? How can it be destroyed?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
