<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>marxism on Alireza Yoonesi</title>
    <link>https://en.AYoonesi.ir/tags/marxism/</link>
    <description>Recent content in marxism on Alireza Yoonesi</description>
    <image>
      <title>Alireza Yoonesi</title>
      <url>https://en.AYoonesi.ir/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://en.AYoonesi.ir/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 14:59:09 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://en.AYoonesi.ir/tags/marxism/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Metamorphosis of Ideals: The Housing Conundrum in a Financial World</title>
      <link>https://en.AYoonesi.ir/posts/metamorphosis-of-ideals-the-housing-conundrum-in-a-financial-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 14:59:09 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://en.AYoonesi.ir/posts/metamorphosis-of-ideals-the-housing-conundrum-in-a-financial-world/</guid>
      <description>In my recent exploration of the United Nations Human Rights Council&amp;#39;s 2017 report on the financialization of housing, authored by Leilani Farha, the Special Rapporteur on the right to adequate housing, I embarked on a scholarly journey that prompted a reevaluation of my convictions regarding governance and societal inequality. The essay challenges the notion of housing as a commodity, contemplates the role of market forces, and addresses the issue of social inequality. It also highlights the significance of liquidity in financial markets and the potential of hedge funds to mitigate systemic risk. Ultimately, the essay seeks to navigate a nuanced path forward in a world where idealism meets the complex realities of housing and finance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Casting Light on the Enigma of Interest Rates: Böhm Bawerk&#39;s Intellectual Journey</title>
      <link>https://en.AYoonesi.ir/posts/casting-light-on-the-enigma-of-interest-rates-b%C3%B6hm-bawerks-intellectual-journey/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 19:37:51 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://en.AYoonesi.ir/posts/casting-light-on-the-enigma-of-interest-rates-b%C3%B6hm-bawerks-intellectual-journey/</guid>
      <description>Delving into the complex world of interest rates, this comprehensive exploration takes us on an intellectual journey guided by the seminal insights of Eugen von Böhm-Bawerk. While economists like Yanis Varoufakis challenge the very essence of interest rates, Böhm-Bawerk&amp;#39;s work provides a fresh perspective, asserting that these rates are not tools of exploitation but rather a natural outcome of human preferences. As we unravel the intricate tapestry of economic theory, we discover the role of time preferences, technological progress, and the pursuit of economic equilibrium. This journey invites readers to delve deeper into the profound world of economics, where the decisions of individuals and institutions shape the destiny of nations, and intellectual curiosity drives relentless exploration.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
