<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><search><entry><title>Projects</title><url>https://linstit.pw/projects/</url><categories/><tags/><content type="html"> I have done not too many projects, but the few are listed down here:
Get Unlimited Medium Articles Using Python (Source Code on GitHub | App) I personally always loved reading, but the problem with reading as a hobby is that you may only have access to some ideas mainly from Scholars or Journalists (or someone else but you get the idea, right?) that ‘MAY’ promote their initial ideas or beliefs with some kind of trick, like supporting a wrong statement with some Psychological experiment done decades ago. Continue Reading</content></entry><entry><title>Best You Can Do To Improve Your Concentration</title><url>https://linstit.pw/post/best-you-can-do-to-improve-your-concentration/</url><categories><category>Medium</category><category>Articles</category><category>Medium</category></categories><tags><tag>Medium</tag><tag>Articles</tag><tag>Free</tag><tag>Creativity</tag><tag>Life</tag><tag>Life Hacks</tag><tag>Productivity</tag></tags><content type="html"> In the modern world, concentration and focus have taken on the characteristics of a dream or even a fantasy. You’re not alone if you’ve ever felt disoriented or uncoordinated while working on something crucial or even when it came down to life or death. I frequently experience this, therefore over the past several months, I have worked many hours to conquer it by remaining focused and dedicated. Please bear with me while I share some advice with you on how to do the same. Concentration? In the modern world, concentration and focus have taken on the characteristics of a dream or even a fantasy. You’re not alone if you’ve ever felt disoriented or uncoordinated while working on something crucial or even when it came down to life or death. I frequently experience this, therefore over the past several months, I have worked many hours to conquer it by remaining focused and dedicated. Please bear with me while I share some advice with you on how to do the same.
In this digital world where our days are full of notifications on our smartphones and different advertisements on our TV screens, it is totally common to feel distracted or not-totally-focused. I’m not trying to make you feel better wasting your time on different social networks, I’m indeed just trying to make it a bit more clear, so don’t use this as a remedy for your feelings of guilt, just my ideas on making my life more productive and make myself 1% more useful every day. So, let’s not waste our time, and better to get it started!
You may read the full article on my Medium.
Since my Medium account has been disabled due to my attempts to make it totally free, all links to my Medium articles are broken now and the full article is available on my Quora</content></entry><entry><title>Get Unlimited Medium Articles Using Python</title><url>https://linstit.pw/post/unlimited-medium-in-python/</url><categories><category>Coding</category><category>Articles</category></categories><tags><tag>Python</tag><tag>Medium</tag><tag>Articles</tag><tag>Free</tag><tag>Creativity</tag></tags><content type="html"> Read unlimited premium Medium articles for free(!) in Python The Idea Let me start my first article on Medium by describing my own problem; I personally always loved reading, but the problem with reading as a hobby is that you may only have access to some ideas mainly from Scholars or Journalists (or someone else but you get the idea, right?) that ‘MAY’ promote their initial ideas or beliefs with some kind of trick, like supporting a wrong statement with some Psychological experiment done decades ago.
This problem is somehow not a problem anymore with the existence of the Internet and its popularity rising every single day. Nowadays you could write almost for free on services like Wordpress.com or Blogger.com but the best system, in my opinion, is Medium.com, which is free to write but not free to read. Though the pricing is too little for an ordinary US citizen, where I come from (Iran) 5 bucks a month is something you cannot pay easily putting its value aside. We are sanctioned, so paying is not an easy option. But every system has different features you could use, right?
You may read the full article on my Medium.
Since my Medium account has been disabled due to my attempts to make it totally free, all links to my Medium articles are broken now and the full article is available on my Quora</content></entry><entry><title>About</title><url>https://linstit.pw/about.html</url><categories/><tags/><content type="html"> I know not much about me or the way I should introduce myself, but the theme I forked from this chinese guy requires some about page so, anyways, I sometimes code mostly in python and javascript, I love linux and I do read sometimes. I read literature, politics, economics and finance and philosophy and whatever I find good. That&rsquo;s enouggh. This site is been publuished using Hugo and the theme is mentioned above. Nothing else matters. P.S.: I write to stay sane.</content></entry><entry><title>Contact ME</title><url>https://linstit.pw/contact.html</url><categories/><tags/><content type="html"> You can contact me using my email which is me@linstit.pw or this link or at the end if you are too lazy the form below:
Loading…</content></entry><entry><title>Dante</title><url>https://linstit.pw/post/dante/</url><categories><category>Culture</category><category>Articles</category></categories><tags><tag>Dante</tag><tag>Devine Comedy</tag><tag>Book</tag><tag>Beatrice</tag><tag>Culture</tag></tags><content type="html"> Dante Alighieri (Italian: [ˈdante aliˈɡjɛːri]), probably baptized Durante di Alighiero degli Alighieri[note 1] and often referred to simply as Dante (/ˈdɑːnteɪ, ˈdænteɪ, ˈdænti/,[2][3] also US: /ˈdɑːnti/;[4] c. 1265 – 14 September 1321), was an Italian[a] poet, writer and philosopher.[6] His Divine Comedy, originally called Comedìa (modern Italian: Commedia) and later christened Divina by Giovanni Boccaccio,[7] is widely considered one of the most important poems of the Middle Ages and the greatest literary work in the Italian language. The New Life Much of the life of Dante Alighieri is obscure, and the known facts are surrounded by a haze of legend and conjecture. He was born in Florence in 1265, of a family noble but not wealthy. His early education is a matter of inference, but we know that he learned the art of writing verse from the poets of France and Provence, and that after he reached manhood he devoted much time to study and became profoundly learned. As a young man he saw military service; and he married some time before he was thirty-two. In Dante&rsquo;s day politics in Florence were exciting and dangerous; and after a few years of participation in public affairs he was condemned to death by his political enemies in 1302. He saved himself by exile, and never returned to his native town. The rest of his life was mainly spent wandering about the north of Italy, in Verona, Bologna, Pisa, Lucca, and finally Ravenna, where he died in 1321. During the years of his exile he found generous patrons in men like the heads of the Scala family in Verona and Guido NovcUo da Polenta in Ravenna; and at Bologna and elsewhere he was welcomed as a teacher. In the early part of the century in which Dante was born, the literary language of Tuscany was still Latin, and not the least of his services to his country was his influence in finally establishing the dignity of Italian as a medium for great literature. He himself used Latin in at least three works: his lecture &ldquo;De Aqua et Terra&rdquo;; his &ldquo;De Monarchia,&rdquo; in which he expounded his political theory of the relation of the Empire and the Papacy; and his unfinished &ldquo;De Vulgari Eloquentia,&rdquo; containing his defense of the use of Italian. More important, however, were his two great works in the vernacular, the &ldquo;Vita Nuova,&rdquo; a series of poems with prose commentary, on his love for Beatrice, and the &ldquo;Divina Commedia.&rdquo;
Bice The Beatrice, real or ideal, who plays so important a part in the poetry of Dante, is stated by Boccaccio to have been the daughter of Folco Portinari, a rich Florentine, and wife of the banker Simone dei Bardi. With this actual person Dante&rsquo;s acquaintance seems to have been of the slightest; but, after the fashion of the chivalric lovers of the day, he took her as the object of his ideal devotion. She became for him, especially after her death in 1290, the center of a mystical devotion of extraordi- nary intensity, and appears in his masterpiece as the personification of heavenly enlightenment.
Dante and Beatrice, by Henry Holiday (1883). Dante looks longingly at Beatrice (in center) passing by with friend Lady Vanna (red) along the Arno River Divine Comedy The &ldquo;Divine Comedy&rdquo; was entitled by Dante himself merely &ldquo;Comediia,&rdquo; &ldquo;meaning a poetic composition in a style intermediate between the sustained nobility of tragedy, and the popular tone of elegy.&rdquo; The word had no dramatic implication at that time, though it did involve a happy ending. The poem is the narrative of a journey down through Hell, up the mountain of Purgatory, and through the revolving heavens into the presence of God. In this aspect it belongs to the two familiar medieval literary types of the Journey and the Vision. It is also an alle- gory, representing under the symbolism of the stages and experiences of the journey, the history of a human soul, painfully struggling from sin through purification to the Beatific Vision. Other schemes of interpre- tation have been worked out and were probably intended, for Dante granted the medieval demand for a threefold and even fourfold signifi- cation in this type of writing. But the &ldquo;Divine Comedy&rdquo; belongs to still other literary forms than those mentioned. Professor Grandgent has pwinted out that it is also an encyclopedia, a poem in praise of Woman, and an autobiography. It contains much of what Dante knew of theology and philosophy, of astronomy and cosmography, and fragments of a number of other branches of learning, so that its encyclopedic character is obvious. In making it a monument to Beatrice, he surpassed infinitely all the poetry devoted to the praise of women in an age when the deification of women was the commonplace of poetry. And finally he made it an autobiography — not a narrative of the external events of his life, but of the agony of his soul.
Dante, poised between the mountain of purgatory and the city of Florence, displays the incipit Nel mezzo del cammin di nostra vita in a detail of Domenico di Michelino's painting, Florence, 1465 He that dies this year is quit for the next / William Shakespeare Thus, in an altogether unique way, Dante summarizes the literature, the philosophy, the science, and the religion of the Middle Ages. Through the intensity of his capacity for exfjerience, the splendor of his power of expression, and the depth of his spiritual and philosophic insight, he at once sums up and transcends a whole era of human history. Dante&rsquo;s final days were spent in Ravenna, where he had been invited to stay in the city in 1318 by its prince, Guido II da Polenta. Dante died in Ravenna on 14 September 1321, aged about 56, of quartan malaria contracted while returning from a diplomatic mission to the Republic of Venice. He was attended by his three children, and possibly by Gemma Donati, and by friends and admirers he had in the city. He was buried in Ravenna at the Church of San Pier Maggiore (later called Basilica di San Francesco). Bernardo Bembo, praetor of Venice, erected a tomb for him in 1483.
On the grave, a verse of Bernardo Canaccio, a friend of Dante, is dedicated to Florence:
Parvi Florentia mater amoris Florence, mother of little love Dante Alieghri tomb in Ravenna, Italy</content></entry></search>