<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><search><entry><title>Web Scraping Series: 01 Intro</title><url>https://linstit.pw/post/web-scraping/</url><categories><category>Programming</category><category>Python</category><category>Articles</category></categories><tags><tag>Web Scraping</tag><tag>Python</tag><tag>Articles</tag><tag>Medium</tag><tag>Programming</tag><tag>Data Science</tag></tags><content type="html"> Data can also be obtained by scraping web pages. It turns out that fetching online pages is simple; obtaining useful structured information from them is more difficult. Intro Putting APIs aside, data may also be obtained through scraping web pages. It turns out that retrieving online pages is quite simple, but extrapolating useful, organized information from them is more difficult.
Let&rsquo;s say you&rsquo;re looking for information on a website. Let&rsquo;s talk a little bit about Milton friedman! How do you behave? You might, however, copy the data from Wikipedia and put it into your own file. But what if you need a website to provide you with a lot of information as rapidly as possible? Using a website&rsquo;s massive volumes of data to train a machine learning algorithm? Copying and pasting won&rsquo;t work in this circumstance! And at that point, web scraping will be required.
Web scraping employs intelligent automation approaches to get hundreds or even millions of data sets in less time than the tedious and time-consuming process of manually gathering data. So let&rsquo;s explore Web scraping in more detail and learn how to apply it to get information from other websites.
What Is Web Scraping? Web scraping is a computerized technique for gathering copious volumes of data from websites. The majority of this data is unstructured in HTML format and is transformed into structured data in a database or spreadsheet so that it may be used in multiple applications. To collect data from websites, web scraping may be done in a variety of methods. These include leveraging specific APIs, online services, or even writing your own code from scratch for web scraping.
You may access the structured data on many huge websites, like Google, Twitter, Facebook, StackOverflow, and others, via their APIs. This is the greatest choice, however there are alternative websites that either lack the technological sophistication or don&rsquo;t let users to access significant volumes of structured data. In that case, it&rsquo;s advisable to employ web scraping to get data from the website.
The scraper and the crawler are the two components needed for web scraping. The crawler is an artificial intelligence system that searches the internet for the specific data needed by clicking on links. On the other hand, the scraper is a unique tool designed to extract data from the website. The scraper&rsquo;s architecture might vary significantly depending on the difficulty and size of the project in order to efficiently and precisely extract the data.
HTML Pages on the web are written in HTML, in which text is (ideally) marked up into elements and their attributes:
&lt;html> &lt;head> &lt;title>A web page&lt;/title> &lt;/head> &lt;body> &lt;p id="author">Alireza Yoonesi&lt;/p> &lt;p id="subject">Machine Learning&lt;/p> &lt;/body> &lt;/html> We would be able to extract data using rules like &ldquo;find the p element whose id is topic and return the text it contains&rdquo; in a perfect world where all web pages were semantically marked up for our convenience. HTML isn&rsquo;t often well-formed or annotated in the real world. Thus, we will require assistance in understanding it.
The Beautiful Soup package, which creates a tree out of the various components on a web page and offers a straightforward interface for accessing them, will be used to extract data from HTML. We&rsquo;ll be using Beautiful Soup 4.11.1 (April 8, 2022), which is the most recent version as of this writing. We’ll also be using the Requests library, which is a much nicer way of making HTTP requests than anything that’s built into Python.
Python’s built-in HTML parser is not that lenient, which means that it doesn’t always cope well with HTML that’s not perfectly formed. For that reason, we’ll also install the html5lib parser.
To Be Continued! You may read the full articles on my Medium.
Did The War In Iraq Create Jobs For Americans?</content></entry><entry><title>Why You Need To Ditch Calling Your Boy/Girl Smart?</title><url>https://linstit.pw/post/why-you-need-to-ditch-calling-your-boy-girl-smart/</url><categories><category>Education</category><category>Books</category><category>Articles</category></categories><tags><tag>Books</tag><tag>Psychology</tag><tag>Articles</tag><tag>medium</tag><tag>Success</tag><tag>Just To Talk About</tag><tag>Depression</tag><tag>Education</tag></tags><content type="html"> This is the story behind my past: My arguments for why no one has the right to call my niece intelligent! As a teenager with more reasons to study hard, I went to a school that needed an entrance exam that appeared tough at first sight but was not too difficult if you studied a little. It was called a branch of “Sampad” which was the short form for The National Organization for Development of Exceptional Talents in Persian. A haven for genius, ideally, but dreams never prove true, do they? This is the story behind my past: My arguments for why no one has the right to call my niece intelligent!
As usual, Manifesto If we divide all people based on their social/economic status into two groups of individuals with Professional (such as lawyers) and Semi-Professional (such as Uber drivers) occupations, we see a significant variation in how these people describe things such as values and expectations.
If you question a truck driver, for example, he or she will most likely insist on outward qualities such as obedience, courtesy, and order. If you ask the same question to a Harvard professor, you will encounter characteristics such as curiosity, pleasure, and cognitive and social maturity. This is one aspect that may influence how these varied parents bond with their children, which usually leads to higher educational objectives.
According to studies conducted between 2002 and 2008, these “Upper-Class” kids are more likely to be involved with alcohol or drugs (such as amphetamine), and the rate of depression among them is extremely high. Furthermore, there was a correlation between drugs and depression and anxiety, leading the researchers to conclude that these students utilized the drugs to treat their depression, resulting in greater and worse drug addiction in the future. (Luthar, Sunia, Columbia University)
You may read the full article on my Medium.
Why You Need To Ditch Calling Your Boy/Girl Smart?</content></entry><entry><title>Did The War In Iraq Create Jobs For Americans?</title><url>https://linstit.pw/post/did-the-war-in-iraq-create-jobs-for-americans/</url><categories><category>Economics</category><category>Politics</category><category>Articles</category></categories><tags><tag>War</tag><tag>Politics</tag><tag>Articles</tag><tag>medium</tag><tag>Economy</tag><tag>Macroeconomics</tag><tag>Political Economy</tag></tags><content type="html"> Is the Iraq War to Blame for the Economic Collapse? War is difficult enough to discuss; the Iraq conflict is far more complicated. Let’s take a different path: Keynesian Economics. Intro? My favorite Outline Generator (Hasan Aboul Hasan’s tool that uses AI to produce outlines for my articles) proposes that I talk about the conflict itself and describe what it was like, etc. I’m assuming you already know everything, and I’d like to examine everything through the lens of macroeconomics. This question was posted on Quora, and it made me think deeply because all of the answers were things like YES, IT DID CERTAINLY, and I was surprised!
The Problem With People One of the issues I have with individuals is that they hardly read. And when they do read, it is usually for titles that aren’t worth their time. This stinks, people, read excellent stuff. In this world, we don’t have much time. I don’t want to waste any more of it on poor books. In any case, I will not be counseling anyone. I begin my talk with a simple question: Have you read Frédéric Bastiat’s That Which Is Seen and That Which Is Not Seen? Obviously not. Let me illustrate this with an example.
You may read the full article on my Medium.
Did The War In Iraq Create Jobs For Americans?</content></entry><entry><title>The Truth About Why Programmers Are More Intelligent Than Doctors?</title><url>https://linstit.pw/post/the-truth-about-why-programmers-are-more-intelligent-than-doctors/</url><categories><category>Medium</category><category>Articles</category><category>Python</category><category>Programming</category></categories><tags><tag>Medium</tag><tag>Articles</tag><tag>Medicine</tag><tag>Doctors</tag><tag>Pyhton</tag><tag>Programming</tag><tag>Science</tag></tags><content type="html"> Doctors Are Smarter Than All? Is That Possible? — And What That Means For You Discussed In Details! In my country, there is a misconception that All doctors are so brilliant or, even more ridiculously, that Doctors are wiser than others. Today, I want to put this myth to the test. Manifesto: Question Description Imagine there is a particular illness called the D, and we have 8 D positives out of every 10,000 people; with a test that is 99% accurate (to clarify, Rapid Covid tests are believed to be 70% reliable/Source). What does a positive test signify in this situation? Let me illustrate; Joe had always known that in medical diagnostics, a positive test signifies you have the disease, a test result means you are not infected, and so on. In fact, a positive is undesirable, and we prefer negatives. Our Joe was walking down the street one day when he came across a banner that read: FREE D TEST! He thought to himself, “If it’s free, I’ll do it.” He received the results after a week. He was both astonished and terrified (D was incurable) because the test did not yield the desired findings! Joe couldn’t tell his family or even his partner about it (can you guess why?).
You may read the full article on my Medium.
I have my Medium account again. YAY.</content></entry><entry><title>Free Medium Articles</title><url>https://linstit.pw/free-medium/</url><categories/><tags/><content type="html"> Free Medium Articles Get Unlimited Medium Articles Using Python (Source Code on GitHub | App) I personally always loved reading, but the problem with reading as a hobby is that you may only have access to some ideas mainly from Scholars or Journalists (or someone else but you get the idea, right?) that ‘MAY’ promote their initial ideas or beliefs with some kind of trick, like supporting a wrong statement with some Psychological experiment done decades ago. Continue Reading Why read Medium? Reading medium articles is an excellent way to learn about new topics or to keep up with current events. When you read a medium article, you’re getting the opinion of the author as well as the information they’ve gathered. This can make it easier to decide whether or not you want to learn more about the topic. In addition, medium articles are often shorter than traditional articles. This makes them more suitable for quick reading. If you have time, you can read the entire article, but reading only a few paragraphs is often enough. Medium also offers a variety of different reading experiences. If you’re looking for a more personal read, you can read the articles on the website itself. If you’d like to read more articles like this, you can also subscribe to a Medium newsletter. This way, you’ll be notified when new articles are published. Reading medium articles is a great way to stay up to date on the current happenings. Medium has provided an active community for folks around the world to share their insights on the world and find audiences for their stories. Writing and of course, reading in Medium increases your productivity and allows you to look at events around the world from a different lens.
Why Does Medium Suck?! And Why Read Medium For Free Though talking about the disadvantages of Medium is just like beating a dead horse’s corpse, my biggest problem with Medium is that it is expensive in my opinion; don’t get me wrong, I don’t think 5$ a month is a huge price for this treasure of knowledge, I just say a corp like Medium mustn’t disallow lots of lives in poorer countries not have access to new days’ science and stories. That’s why I developed this tool. You may use the form below to read unlimited premium articles for free. Continue Reading Here On Other Ways To Read Medium For Free</content></entry><entry><title>Projects</title><url>https://linstit.pw/projects/</url><categories/><tags/><content type="html"> With no special order: I have done not too many projects, but the few are listed down here:
Get Unlimited Medium Articles Using Python (Source Code on GitHub | App) I personally always loved reading, but the problem with reading as a hobby is that you may only have access to some ideas mainly from Scholars or Journalists (or someone else but you get the idea, right?) that ‘MAY’ promote their initial ideas or beliefs with some kind of trick, like supporting a wrong statement with some Psychological experiment done decades ago. Continue Reading
Instagram Profile Get for Telegram (Source Code on GitHub) A simple project that fetches IG profiles in HD quality, it gained no serious attention on the Internet, so I just deleted the repository on my servers. But the source code is available. It could be easily used with flask, too. Just delete the Telegram options and add Flask to it. Simple.
Hugo Theme That My Site Uses(GutHub Source) A theme translated to Persian. Main Theme Here
YouTube WordCloud with Flask in Python(GutHub Source) The idea is creating wordcloud for YouTube videos, and then Medium articles as well. I copied the idea from this guy btw. I used word_cloud from PyPi, lots of thanks to amueller for his effort on this project. It produces something like this out of YouTube videos:</content></entry><entry><title>Best You Can Do To Improve Your Concentration</title><url>https://linstit.pw/post/best-you-can-do-to-improve-your-concentration/</url><categories><category>Medium</category><category>Articles</category><category>Medium</category></categories><tags><tag>Medium</tag><tag>Articles</tag><tag>Free</tag><tag>Creativity</tag><tag>Life</tag><tag>Life Hacks</tag><tag>Productivity</tag></tags><content type="html"> In the modern world, concentration and focus have taken on the characteristics of a dream or even a fantasy. You’re not alone if you’ve ever felt disoriented or uncoordinated while working on something crucial or even when it came down to life or death. I frequently experience this, therefore over the past several months, I have worked many hours to conquer it by remaining focused and dedicated. Please bear with me while I share some advice with you on how to do the same. Concentration? In the modern world, concentration and focus have taken on the characteristics of a dream or even a fantasy. You’re not alone if you’ve ever felt disoriented or uncoordinated while working on something crucial or even when it came down to life or death. I frequently experience this, therefore over the past several months, I have worked many hours to conquer it by remaining focused and dedicated. Please bear with me while I share some advice with you on how to do the same.
In this digital world where our days are full of notifications on our smartphones and different advertisements on our TV screens, it is totally common to feel distracted or not-totally-focused. I’m not trying to make you feel better wasting your time on different social networks, I’m indeed just trying to make it a bit more clear, so don’t use this as a remedy for your feelings of guilt, just my ideas on making my life more productive and make myself 1% more useful every day. So, let’s not waste our time, and better to get it started!
You may read the full article on my Medium.
Since my Medium account has been disabled due to my attempts to make it totally free, all links to my Medium articles are broken now and the full article is available on my Quora</content></entry><entry><title>Get Unlimited Medium Articles Using Python</title><url>https://linstit.pw/post/unlimited-medium-in-python/</url><categories><category>Coding</category><category>Articles</category></categories><tags><tag>Python</tag><tag>Medium</tag><tag>Articles</tag><tag>Free</tag><tag>Creativity</tag></tags><content type="html"> Read unlimited premium Medium articles for free(!) in Python The Idea Let me start my first article on Medium by describing my own problem; I personally always loved reading, but the problem with reading as a hobby is that you may only have access to some ideas mainly from Scholars or Journalists (or someone else but you get the idea, right?) that ‘MAY’ promote their initial ideas or beliefs with some kind of trick, like supporting a wrong statement with some Psychological experiment done decades ago.
This problem is somehow not a problem anymore with the existence of the Internet and its popularity rising every single day. Nowadays you could write almost for free on services like Wordpress.com or Blogger.com but the best system, in my opinion, is Medium.com, which is free to write but not free to read. Though the pricing is too little for an ordinary US citizen, where I come from (Iran) 5 bucks a month is something you cannot pay easily putting its value aside. We are sanctioned, so paying is not an easy option. But every system has different features you could use, right?
You may read the full article on my Medium.
Since my Medium account has been disabled due to my attempts to make it totally free, all links to my Medium articles are broken now and the full article is available on my Quora</content></entry><entry><title>About</title><url>https://linstit.pw/about/</url><categories/><tags/><content type="html"> I am a developer I suffer therefore I exist.
Just like doves. That is all.
I know not much about me or the way I should introduce myself, but the theme I forked from this chinese guy requires some about page so, anyways, I sometimes code mostly in python and javascript, I love linux and I do read sometimes. I read literature, politics, economics and finance and philosophy and whatever I find good. That&rsquo;s enouggh. This site is been publuished using Hugo and the theme is mentioned above. Nothing else matters. P.S.: I write to stay sane.
I develope Python programs, mostly web apps backend (Django, Flask &amp; FastAPI) and Artificial Intelligence(AI, ML, DS). Somedays I do use JavaScript and NodeJS (mostly express and nuxt) but it&rsquo;s not my cup of tea. I know some C++ and I have experience in Linux servers (doing devops things). I&rsquo;m available remotely cuze I live in Iran. (:
Check my projects here and my GitHub here.</content></entry><entry><title>Contact</title><url>https://linstit.pw/contact/</url><categories/><tags/><content type="html"> You can reach me via email at me@linstit.pw, this Google Form, or, if you&rsquo;re as lazy as I am, the form below:
Loading…</content></entry><entry><title>Dante</title><url>https://linstit.pw/post/dante/</url><categories><category>Culture</category><category>Articles</category></categories><tags><tag>Dante</tag><tag>Devine Comedy</tag><tag>Book</tag><tag>Beatrice</tag><tag>Culture</tag></tags><content type="html"> Dante Alighieri (Italian: [ˈdante aliˈɡjɛːri]), probably baptized Durante di Alighiero degli Alighieri[note 1] and often referred to simply as Dante (/ˈdɑːnteɪ, ˈdænteɪ, ˈdænti/,[2][3] also US: /ˈdɑːnti/;[4] c. 1265 – 14 September 1321), was an Italian[a] poet, writer and philosopher.[6] His Divine Comedy, originally called Comedìa (modern Italian: Commedia) and later christened Divina by Giovanni Boccaccio,[7] is widely considered one of the most important poems of the Middle Ages and the greatest literary work in the Italian language. The New Life Much of the life of Dante Alighieri is obscure, and the known facts are surrounded by a haze of legend and conjecture. He was born in Florence in 1265, of a family noble but not wealthy. His early education is a matter of inference, but we know that he learned the art of writing verse from the poets of France and Provence, and that after he reached manhood he devoted much time to study and became profoundly learned. As a young man he saw military service; and he married some time before he was thirty-two. In Dante&rsquo;s day politics in Florence were exciting and dangerous; and after a few years of participation in public affairs he was condemned to death by his political enemies in 1302. He saved himself by exile, and never returned to his native town. The rest of his life was mainly spent wandering about the north of Italy, in Verona, Bologna, Pisa, Lucca, and finally Ravenna, where he died in 1321. During the years of his exile he found generous patrons in men like the heads of the Scala family in Verona and Guido NovcUo da Polenta in Ravenna; and at Bologna and elsewhere he was welcomed as a teacher. In the early part of the century in which Dante was born, the literary language of Tuscany was still Latin, and not the least of his services to his country was his influence in finally establishing the dignity of Italian as a medium for great literature. He himself used Latin in at least three works: his lecture &ldquo;De Aqua et Terra&rdquo;; his &ldquo;De Monarchia,&rdquo; in which he expounded his political theory of the relation of the Empire and the Papacy; and his unfinished &ldquo;De Vulgari Eloquentia,&rdquo; containing his defense of the use of Italian. More important, however, were his two great works in the vernacular, the &ldquo;Vita Nuova,&rdquo; a series of poems with prose commentary, on his love for Beatrice, and the &ldquo;Divina Commedia.&rdquo;
Bice The Beatrice, real or ideal, who plays so important a part in the poetry of Dante, is stated by Boccaccio to have been the daughter of Folco Portinari, a rich Florentine, and wife of the banker Simone dei Bardi. With this actual person Dante&rsquo;s acquaintance seems to have been of the slightest; but, after the fashion of the chivalric lovers of the day, he took her as the object of his ideal devotion. She became for him, especially after her death in 1290, the center of a mystical devotion of extraordi- nary intensity, and appears in his masterpiece as the personification of heavenly enlightenment.
Dante and Beatrice, by Henry Holiday (1883). Dante looks longingly at Beatrice (in center) passing by with friend Lady Vanna (red) along the Arno River Divine Comedy The &ldquo;Divine Comedy&rdquo; was entitled by Dante himself merely &ldquo;Comediia,&rdquo; &ldquo;meaning a poetic composition in a style intermediate between the sustained nobility of tragedy, and the popular tone of elegy.&rdquo; The word had no dramatic implication at that time, though it did involve a happy ending. The poem is the narrative of a journey down through Hell, up the mountain of Purgatory, and through the revolving heavens into the presence of God. In this aspect it belongs to the two familiar medieval literary types of the Journey and the Vision. It is also an alle- gory, representing under the symbolism of the stages and experiences of the journey, the history of a human soul, painfully struggling from sin through purification to the Beatific Vision. Other schemes of interpre- tation have been worked out and were probably intended, for Dante granted the medieval demand for a threefold and even fourfold signifi- cation in this type of writing. But the &ldquo;Divine Comedy&rdquo; belongs to still other literary forms than those mentioned. Professor Grandgent has pwinted out that it is also an encyclopedia, a poem in praise of Woman, and an autobiography. It contains much of what Dante knew of theology and philosophy, of astronomy and cosmography, and fragments of a number of other branches of learning, so that its encyclopedic character is obvious. In making it a monument to Beatrice, he surpassed infinitely all the poetry devoted to the praise of women in an age when the deification of women was the commonplace of poetry. And finally he made it an autobiography — not a narrative of the external events of his life, but of the agony of his soul.
Dante, poised between the mountain of purgatory and the city of Florence, displays the incipit Nel mezzo del cammin di nostra vita in a detail of Domenico di Michelino's painting, Florence, 1465 He that dies this year is quit for the next / William Shakespeare Thus, in an altogether unique way, Dante summarizes the literature, the philosophy, the science, and the religion of the Middle Ages. Through the intensity of his capacity for exfjerience, the splendor of his power of expression, and the depth of his spiritual and philosophic insight, he at once sums up and transcends a whole era of human history. Dante&rsquo;s final days were spent in Ravenna, where he had been invited to stay in the city in 1318 by its prince, Guido II da Polenta. Dante died in Ravenna on 14 September 1321, aged about 56, of quartan malaria contracted while returning from a diplomatic mission to the Republic of Venice. He was attended by his three children, and possibly by Gemma Donati, and by friends and admirers he had in the city. He was buried in Ravenna at the Church of San Pier Maggiore (later called Basilica di San Francesco). Bernardo Bembo, praetor of Venice, erected a tomb for him in 1483.
On the grave, a verse of Bernardo Canaccio, a friend of Dante, is dedicated to Florence:
Parvi Florentia mater amoris Florence, mother of little love Dante Alieghri tomb in Ravenna, Italy</content></entry></search>